Will he find out?
The president arranged this date because he is interested in my older sister right?
Do I look 23 years old?
Well, his eyes aren't that good so maybe we can trick him.
That being said, this good deed will get us ahead.
The other party is the Takaba group. The biggest conglomerate.
My older sister has a boyfriend right now!
Having your daughter marry someone just for a high status is shameful!
Stop acting like you know everything!
Listen up!
Don't contradict me here!
You need to speak politely.
Do you understand?
Well, since this is an arranged date..
He's probably a dwarf that nobody likes.
My older sister is always right.
Pardon us.
We can start the arranged date.
Thanks for waiting Nonomura-kun.
Yes! Today I was granted a favor and I have come to offer my daughter from my Charcoal company!
I'm very grateful for this opportunity!
Sorry about asking you for this favor out of nowhere.
Takane. Hurry and come in.
I didn't expect him to be a hottie! What am I going to do?
This is my grandson Takane.
Wow...this is Takaba Takane-sama!
Thank you for today. Please take care of you...me.
Of me..
It's not Takaba!
I'm Saibara Takane.
Oh no...what have I done?
Please forgive me!
Now, now.
This is my daughter Yukari.
Nice to meet you Yukari-san.
Please take care of me.
They're such outstanding young people!
They are prefect for each other!
A normal and humble girl is more suitable for him.
In the near future Takane...is going to be the head of the Takaba group.
He is still not familiar with a lot of things.
In order for him to work harder he needs to have some good help.
Thank you!
Come on Takane. Greet them too.
This person doesn't look like her pictures at all!
Way too much makeup!
Young people from the big cities wear makeup nowadays.
I really dislike women who put on such thick layers of makeup in order to seduce men.
What are you saying?
Your face is not going to look any better even if you smile.
Takane!
Even if you wear a fancy Kimono that normal people have access too...
Did you think my family would start emptying our pockets for you?
You sure underestimated me didn't you?
That's enough!
She's just a gold digger trying to get some big bucks!
What kind of nonsense are you saying?
Shut the hell up and open those little ears for me!
Hana...no...Yukari! Yukari!
Sorry but...
I don't have the slightest interest in you at all big boy!
Hana!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! Umm..
I'm sorry about this...
Translated, subbed and timed by Rjgman56.
My Dad probably got fired from his company...
It's okay!
Right, Mizuki?
That's right!
Let's go to Okamoto's place to cheer you up!
Let's do that!
Hey! Look at that car!
Isn't that amazing?
Do you know him?
He was at the arranged date yesterday.
Is he the rich heir?
He's coming over here!
You over there!
You really played me the other day at the arranged date.
And you're still a high school student...
How did you find out?
Who do you think I am?
The heir to the Takaba group?
That is me!
And I've come out of my way to see you.
I didn't ask you to though!
Wh...
I'll give this to you.
You've never gotten such a gorgeous bouquet of flowers before right?
I refuse! Pardon me!
Wait!
You came here to get revenge on me for yesterday right?
You're easy to read!
Does your Dad really want to quit his job I wonder?
Is this black mail?
You want him to work until he retires right?
Now then! Get in!
Sorry! I'll be going okay?
What's going on?
I don't know.
Hana had an arranged date with him.
An arranged date?
Saiba-sama.
Thanks for waiting.
Go ahead.
I cannot accept these expensive clothes.
Who said that I was going to give them to you? You're so cheeky!
You probably don't know this but...
This restaurant has a dress code that you need to follow.
Yeah, yeah! I didn't know that anyways!
Did you say anything?
No!
This is super premium Kobe beef.
This is the first time I've seen someone eat it like a pig!
Is that a thank you I hear?
You've probably never eaten this before have you?
Close your mouth and eat it, porky!
It is true that you have to eat high quality food more neatly.
But why did you invite me out anyways?
You found out that I'm in high school.
I don't have anything to do with you anymore!
Is it because you're a lonely boy?
Let me tell you something!
I've never been bothered by women!
You said it didn't you?
I'm coming to get my sweet revenge!
You're not going to tell me that you don't like tomatoes right?
Are you a little kid?
I'll eat them later.
You're a little kid!
It's not good if you don't eat them!
Tomatoes have Lycopene which can help reduce fatigue.
I'm different than the average person who refuses to eat them.
I want to enjoy the taste of the tomatoes on the side instead of blended with everything else.
I'm not the same as you!
Thanks for the meal!
I'll give you back these clothes after I wash them.
It's fine.
You can have them.
But you just said..
Yesterday...
I said that you were wearing too much makeup...
And I said a lot of unreasonable things.
Sorry....
I said I'm sorry!
After all of that...I heard that my grandfather was the one who arranged all of it.
I'm deeply sorry as well for what I did.
Later.
Umm...Is it possible...
That you came here to make amends?
Like hell I did!
Alright, I'm going!
I'm home.
What's up with those clothes?
Did you do something bad?
There's no way that I did!
I met Takane-san.
Takane-san?
From yesterday?
He's not angry?
That's what it seems like.
He's not?
I'll see you again on your next off day. You don't have to wear your clown makeup.
Good afternoon.
Wow, you have a talent for looking plain.
This is how I normally dress.
Is this how poor people dress?
It's a popular fashion style!
By the way Takane-san. What kind of job are you going to pursue?
What the?
I thought you didn't have any interest in me sweety?
You really are a rich second generation boy.
You just have your parents throw all their money on your lap.
You live your life without any worries.
You really have the mouth of the devil himself.
You have pretty high specs and you should be popular...
But I wonder why you're the lone ranger over here?
Women are just a bunch of gold diggers!
There's a reason why you're so popular with gold diggers.
It's because the only thing you have going for you is your money.
What does a little preschooler like you know about someone like me?
Welcome!
I'll take your order.
I'll get the beef meal set.
Yes.
I'll have the spaghetti with tomato sauce meal set.
Understood.
Tomato...
Please meet my older sister next time.
She's a beautiful girl that would have no problem dating someone foul mouthed like you.
You guys are the same age and your personalities suit each other. Like two peas in a pod.
Well...she does have a boyfriend so she might reject you though.
So basically you are saying that someone like you doesn't deserve to be with me?
How far is your head up your butt?
It's fine isn't it?
You have an inferiority complex, I get it.
Everyone has been biased towards me and your older sister.
What the heck?
Inferiority is a good thing.
Sometimes people aren't satisfied with the way that things are and achieve great things.
Do you have some kind of complex as well?
I do.
Yeah right!
Having a complex is impossible for someone like me!
You are a rich boy after all.
Everything is smooth sailing for you but I'm hitting all your points today.
I'm so happy that I'm an ordinary person!
Don't worry.
Even you have your good points.
You have that fierceness and wise-ass attitude that just hits the spot.
That isn't a compliment!
I have come out of my way to see you again.
Be more confident.
You were so happy when I told you that weren't you?
Not in a million years!
Saibara-kun..
General manager!
Good work!
Are you on a date by any chance?
That isn't the case.
Hey Saibara-kun.
You're the only heir to the Takaba group.
Shouldn't you pick someone with a better appeal and charm?
You don't need to worry about that.
Thank you for today.
Takane-san.
Do you want to stop seeing each other?
It doesn't matter how you say it.
But isn't the arranged date already over?
We lied to the president as well.
Things like getting married is out of the question.
Is this about what was said earlier?
You don't have any right to end the date.
But...
If you're going to fall for me...
Then feel free to back out.
Do you understand?
Now what?
What do you do after you pin me against the wall?
After?
Are you supposed to do something after the kabedon?
Geez! If you don't know what to do then don't do it!
That's so 2008.
There was a mosquito right next to your face and so I wanted to hit it!
Is it because someone here smells like curry?
You're pretty interesting Takane-san!
Interesting?
I'm a full fledged badass!
Open up those eyes and take a good look!
Oh that's right!
This is a little late but here is my thank you gift.
This is really popular right now.
What the heck is this?
Is that food?
Good night!
Isn't this rubber?
It's not bad.
Should I borrow this from my sister?
Isn't this a little too sudden?
That's going to scare away men isn't it?
Really?
I'm home!
Welcome home!
Hana. Takane-san is going to come and pick you up tomorrow right?
I'm going to go on a date with him!
What about your boyfriend?
I broke up with him!
That being said, I'm going to go after Takane-san with everything I've got!
You broke up!?
Are you serious Yukari? Alright!!
If you like someone that much can you really just end things like that?
Hana...
The time spent with another person isn't that long.
It would be a waste to let this opportunity pass us by right?
That being said Hana...
Good work!
I think that Takane-san is going to accept and marry me!
Is that so?
That means that everything is reset back to normal. Aren't you glad Hana?
Do you want to go to Okamoto's place again today?
Let's go! Let's go!
I want to hear about Hana's date too!
That's true! I wanna hear all about it!
It's going to be so fun!
Alright, we'll have the tempura with pork and shrimp! Please!
You're going to have that again?
We have a huge menu here!
Take a good luck at it!
I'm home.
Welcome home Okamoto!
Welcome home! Good work today!
You guys came again?
Souma! That's not what you say!
These are our precious guests after all!
It's fine! It's just them after all.
Don't say that!
Well...whatever.
It looks so yummy!
Go ahead!
It's hot so be careful.
Thanks for the food!
So how did the date with the hottie go?
He's an amazing person isn't he?
He's amazing?
He graduated from the Tokyo university.
Then he got an MBA at Harvard university.
And I heard that he is the heir to the big Takaba group!
You know your stuff.
I checked him out because I'm very curious.
It's Hana's first love.
He isn't my boyfriend!
You go on dates with him though!
They're not dates!
Is that right?
I think he's your type though Hana.
He's not my type at all!
He's a huge narcissist.
And he isn't interested in me at all.
Even though he brought you a ton of roses?
He doesn't know my name does he?
He never asked me!
That sounds pretty lonely.
He just thinks that I'm interesting because I didn't act in the way that he expected me too.
This is how rich people have fun. It's like a game to him.
Then you aren't going to see him anymore?
Of course not!
He's on a date with my older sister right now anyways.
Why?
I have no clue!
Well...he was a potential marriage partner for your older sister at first anyways.
Hana's older sister is a babe too!
A son from a rich family like him is a dime in a dozen.
Aren't you lucky that you got to meet him?
How am I lucky?
Being with that guy was a waste of time!
I'm glad that I don't have to see him anymore!
Don't worry.
You have your good points too.
I came out of my way to see you again.
Be more confident.
You have no right to end the date.
But...
If you're going to fall for me...then feel free to back out.
Do you understand?
Hana...
Did I say something that upset you?
No...
I wonder why?
Oh! It's this! It's this!
Okamo...
It seems like your cooking was so good today it brought me to tears.
What are you doing Okamoto?
That hurt...
She's laughing...
When someone is sad or worried, it's all in their head right?
But if you are distracted by something else then you won't think about it.
What kind of theory is that?
It is true that I had those kinds of thoughts.
It was just for a second though.
See?
It's been a while!
Do you want some more?
Go ahead! Go ahead!
Welcome!
Hey...why are you here?
What about you Takane-san?
What about my older sister?
I didn't have a potential marriage date with your older sister. I had one with you!
Sorry, just take this.
Let's go! Hurry up!
Hold on!
How is it?
I picked a place that I thought you would like.
My older sister probably rejected you huh?
It's not a surprise with that attitude you have.
I've never been rejected once in my life!
I was the one you were supposed to meet on that day.
But I was feeling sick and so I sent my little sister instead...
Please call your little sister over here.
She went out though...
What?
Like I said...I was the one that you were supposed to see...
I'm deeply sorry.
But I don't have the slightest interest in you at all!
But more importantly...where is your sister?
Like I said, you should accept me as your...
Hurry up and tell me!!
Yes!
You're bothering me!
Bothering you?
I mean...the way that you just do things on your own...
I understand your feelings!
Be honest.
How do you feel about me?
Su...su..su..
Su?
You're SU-per annoying!
How can you say that?
You're troublesome!
Are you even able to say something cute?
Takane-san.
You're a fool for worrying about me over my sister.
I don't need your pity.
There's no way someone like me would feel pity!
I'm interested in you.
Hana. That's your name right?
My name...
Stop teasing me!
On our potential marriage date you pretended to be your older sister who is 7 years older than you.
That is fraud!
You made me so mad that I ran out of there.
I gave you a rose bouquet.
I let you eat high quality steak.
But you wouldn't fall for me.
This is the first time I've had a woman make me this frustrated.
I'll show you what to do after you do a Kabedon.